good morning scobie's my room but trying
to vacuum the floor
oh yeah get in there get every corner
what up drinking a amante I got scope
he's one hand they got Mata and the
other a laptop in my back
it's morning guys I love morning
mornings my favorite tired day seriously
nobody's awake yet to ask me questions
no questions mornings I wake up maybe
I'll play a little chess maybe I'll read
a little bit I've been reading Jordan
Peterson's book it's pretty good yeah
early scope yeah so I might lose some
reception when I walked out right on my
talks at 9:45 come find it
come find it I'm going to be talking
about pandas neons and , and you know
I'm dropping fire right you always drop
fire alright will it be online I don't
know but I will tweet out the fire part
of the talk after it's done oh I love
super hearts man yeah I know
well okay so but I'm also doing a
workshop apparently I'm not really sure
what that is but I'm doing a workshop at
1:00 p.m. so if you guys are around for
that that is an option as well took my
MOT a laptop of my back on my air pods
in my pocket I bought a new pair of ear
pods read this survey this morning our
Tesla is the most trusted brand in
self-driving cars interesting to think
about
no no no we got fire man we got fire you
know a fire is we don't talk about what
fire is yeah we'll talk about what fire
is afterward
I'm common next hey maybe I don't know
do I look like the kind of guy who can
be trusted I don't know about that um ah
there's a different pass for Expo and
speaking I don't know man I don't know
who actually goes to these conferences
probably people who want to get away
from their shitty jobs I don't blame you
find a shitty job and there's 72
conferences
I go - yeah I'm gonna learn about the
Cyberman the cyber security notice how
everything that puts cyber in front of
his bullshit but even wired said that so
that's kind of bullshit I'm quoting the
news here the media safety support an
actual safety you know it's not
important talking about safety so I'm
not gonna talk about it anymore
am I on something you people always
think I'm on drugs I'm not on drugs most
of the time sometimes I am people think
I'm more normal maybe but no no no just
just woke up submit my mottai you know
when I smoke and get like normal man
this is the Hyper's is just the hyper is
just my life I got to have a lot of
energy good bye
all right so we're gonna buy a Muni
ticket you guys on bottom you need to
take it with me taking the Muni downtown
they miss the Muni ones the next Muni
come heels good ma'am
another interesting thing that about
that survey was wammo wasn't very highly
rated and you don't really think like
how much does Google believe in their
crap if they won't call it Google right
alright let's buy Muni ticket by Muni
ticket adult single trip okay now let's
put $3 and OH
oh man let's go let's go let's go
I should just have Muni tickets you know
[Music]
take my dollar
sweet
[Music]
this community to go let's go let's go
let's go no I don't need to repeat only
my quarter just little homeless yeah
let's roll
oh man that pew meets packed so no one
really knows you can watch the way about
cars they drive like grandma's alright
scobie's I'm sure I'm gonna lose you
when we go in the Muni oh man oh man
excuse me